你们俩确定要进去吗?
Are you sure you two want to go in there?
‐这房子煞气重的很 ‐这正是
‐That place was built above the devil's asshole. ‐That is why
‐我们要进去的原因 ‐这是洛杉矶最恐怖的凶宅
‐we are going in. ‐It's the most haunted house in Los Angeles.
可能也是全美最恐怖的
Probably the entire United States.
注释：Village（格林威治村的死亡之屋）：悬疑鼻祖爱伦·坡在这里写出短小精悍的惊险故事。
紧随其后的是格林威治村的死亡之屋
Followed closely by the House of Death in Greenwich Village,
注释：Cleveland（克利夫兰的富兰克林城堡）：被认为是俄亥俄州最闹鬼最凶的房子。1985年建造者的一整家人都死于非命。
克利夫兰的富兰克林城堡 当然还有……
the Franklin Castle in Cleveland and, of course...
注释：Orleans（新奥尔良的拉劳里宅邸）：当时有传闻说这对夫妇恶毒的对待他们的黑奴。
《美国恐怖故事第三季》：女巫会有关于戴尔芬·拉劳里对奴隶进行残酷的折磨的场景。
新奥尔良的拉劳里宅邸
The LaLaurie Mansion in New Orleans.
谎言!谎言!
Lies! Lies!
我们是《美国恐怖故事》的狂热粉丝
We are, like, huge American Horror Story fans.
我听说这关于这座房子的不好传闻
I hear bad stuff about this house.
我带你们去旅馆怎么样?
How about I take you to a hotel?
注释：Cortez（科泰兹旅馆）：《美国恐怖故事第五季：旅馆》故事发生地，灵感来源于塞西尔酒店（因高犯罪率与蓝可儿案声名狼藉，已更名并关闭）
你是说科泰兹旅馆吗?
You mean like the Hotel Cortez?
不 我们很好 我们特意租了这屋子过夜
No, we're good. We rented this place out for the night.
注释：Airbnb（爱彼迎）：全球民宿短租公寓预订平台。
‐现在有爱彼迎 ‐房主提供
‐It's an Airbnb now. ‐The owners offer
一整套"谋杀屋逃离记"
this whole "Escape from the Murder House Experience."
肯定惊恐刺激极了
It's supposed to be super chilling.
他们保证我们会吓得一夜无眠
They promise we will not sleep a wink.
我们是那种狂热的恐怖迷
We're, like, huge horror fans in general.
我们是几年前在动漫展上认识的
We met a couple years back at Comic‐Con.
注释：Son of Bloody Face（血脸杀手之子）：出自《美国恐怖故事第二季：疯人院》
我扮成血脸杀手之子
I was dressed as Son of Bloody Face,
注释：Sister Jude（裘德修女）：出自《美国恐怖故事第二季：疯人院》
她打扮成裘德修女的样子
and she was dressed as Sister Jude.
我们一见钟情
It was love at first sight.
随你们便 但到时候别说我没提醒过你们
Whatever. But don't say I didn't warn you.
‐等等 ‐怎么了?
‐Wait. ‐What?
‐你改变主意了吗?‐没有
‐You having second thoughts? ‐No.
不 我只是想好好的感受一下这座房子
No. I just want to feel it
在预备好的恐怖盛宴开始之前
before all the preplanned crazy starts.
我想感受一下一下这座房子蕴涵的能量
I just want to feel the energy of the house.
怎么了?
What?
没什么
Nothing.
没什么 我想我只是兴奋过头了
Nothing. I think I'm just so psyched,
我有点儿入戏过早了
I'm getting a bit ahead of myself.
来吧 我们去一探究竟
Come on. Let's go explore.
“欢迎来到谋杀屋
"Welcome to Murder House.
“如果你们像那些可怜的灵魂那样
"If you're anything like every other poor soul
进入高墙之内后 就可能会被永远困在这里”
that entered these walls, you may get stuck here forever."
这封信背后有写东西
There's something on the back of the note.
注释：Violatate指的是《美国恐怖故事第一季：谋杀屋》中的一对恋人：维奥莱特·哈蒙与哈特·兰登。Violataters则是这对恋人cp粉。
“我们听说你们是‘维奥塔特’的cp粉
"We hear you're 'Violataters.'
“你的下一趟冒险之旅是去找到
"Your next adventure is to find
"塔特与她初遇之处 和
"the room where Tate first appeared to her and they later
"他们缠绵枕侧 陷入致命的禁忌之爱的房间
"consummated their forbidden and fateful love.
“跟随黑玫瑰花瓣洒落的痕迹
"Follow the black rose petals
有胆你就来”
if you dare."
噢 上帝 这真是绝了
Oh, my God. This is amazing.
是啊
Yeah.
敬这个让我梦想成真的男人
To the man who makes my dreams come true,
即使那是噩梦
even if they're nightmares.
噢
Oh.
尝起来像……血
Tastes like... blood.
美妙极了
Awesome.
‐我们开始冒险吧 ‐好啊
‐Let's play. ‐Yeah.
这也太毛骨悚然了
This is so sick.
等等 谁把这些蜡烛点燃的?
Wait, who lit the candles?
你有没有感觉房子里除了我们还有其他人?
Do you think there's someone in the house with us?
肯定有啊 对吧?就像闹鬼的干草车
There's got to be, right? Like the haunted hayrides.
我感觉我们应该准备好
I feel like we should be prepared
接受一些突如其来的惊吓了
for a few jump scares.
等等 他们可能在墙后的
Wait, maybe they're in the tunnels
地道里
behind the walls.
呃 我觉得那只是存在于电视剧中
Uh, I think that's just in the show.
现实中的房子不会真的有这种设置
Don't think that's actually in the house.
注释：Larry Harver（拉里·哈维）：《美国恐怖故事第一季：谋杀屋》中的人物之一，他在恶灵的指示下烧死了他全家。
也许是拉里·哈维
Maybe it was Larry Harvey and he used
让他其中一个被烧死的孩子来点的
one of his smoldering children to light them.
准备好来点换装游戏了吗?
Up for a little cosplay?
见鬼
Holy shit.
不 不 不 别脱
No, no, no, no. Leave it on.
磨人的小妖精
Kinky.
对不起
Sorry.
你觉得为什么人们
Why do you think people like
这么喜欢恐怖故事呢?
scary stories so much?
嗯 他们一直都很喜欢
Well, they always have.
假扮怪物 让我们遗忘真实的怪物
Pretend monsters let us forget about the real ones.
你们会死在里面的
You're gonna die in here.
我的天啊 一定有扬声器
My gosh. There must be a speaker
藏在这个房间的某个角落 太酷了
hidden somewhere in this room. That is so cool.
你有没有觉得房子里除了我们还有其他人?
Do you think there's someone in the house with us?
‐我们去看看 ‐好
‐Let's go see. ‐Okay.
‐怎么了? ‐我不知道
‐What's the matter? ‐I don't know.
我好像站不起来了
I can't seem to get up.
怎么回事?
What?
噢 上帝啊
Oh, my God.
来吧 我们去一探究竟
Come on, let's go check it out.
说不定我还能找到个鬼
Maybe I could find a ghost
能更持久的来两发呢
that'll last more than two pumps.
他们拍这集的灵感来源于
They based this episode
注释：Richard Speck（理查德·斯派克）：出自《美国恐怖故事第一季：谋杀屋》
on Richard Speck.
你知道的
You know,
他是谋杀护士的连环杀手
he's the serial killer that murdered all those nurses.
是啊 我们可是在恐怖迷大会上认识的
Yeah. We met at a horror convention.
‐你认为我会不知道吗? ‐好
‐You think I don't know that? ‐Okay.
‐好吧 ‐怎么了?
‐Okay. ‐What?
我想 我们现在是时候
I'm guessing this is the part
签署那些弃权书了
where we have to sign all those waivers
“警告 签署后
is gonna start. "Warning. By signing this,
“即接受了相关责任的豁免
"you accept that you absolve all knowledge
“对于此次《谋杀屋逃离记》体验
"of anything that can happen to your mind, body or psyche
"对身体或心智造成的任何伤害
"during your time in the experience
‐出现意外概不负责” ‐我知道
‐of the Escape from the Murder House Experience." ‐I know.
说说而已 这是我们最后的机会
Just saying, this is our last chance.
你知道 我们当然也可以回归日常生活 吃点煎饼
You know, we could always go to Norms, get some pancakes,
注释：Roanoke:即《美国恐怖故事第六季：洛亚诺克》
直接回家 一口气连看几集《洛亚诺克》
go home, binge‐watch Roanoke.
注释：Sarah Paulson（莎拉·保尔森）：《美国恐怖故事》常驻演员，编辑和导演。
为什么莎拉·保尔森大骂那一季?
Why does Sarah Paulson shit‐talk that season?
明明非常出彩
It's so good.
你真的想回去看《洛亚诺克》吗
Do you really want to go watch Roanoke?
不 我要吓得屁滚尿流了呢
No. I want to shit myself 'cause I'm so scared.
‐我也是 ‐ 来吧
‐Me, too. ‐Come on.
来吧
Come on.
嘘
Shh.
你听见了吗?
Do you hear that?
‐救救我们 求你们了! ‐求求你们了
‐Help us, please! ‐Please,
‐救救我们! ‐她们是谁啊
‐help us! ‐Who the hell are they?
我们是不是少看了一集吗?
Did we miss an episode?
抱歉 你们是?
I'm sorry, who are you?
不好意思 你们是从哪一集里来的?
Yeah, sorry, which episode are you guys from?
你们在说什么?
What are you talking about?
十年前 我们上门玩“不给糖就捣蛋”的游戏
Ten years ago, we went trick‐or‐treating.
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick or treat.
女孩们 你们不会想进来的
You girls don't want to be here.
熟男警告
DILF alert.
你可以给我们点糖果
You can give us some candy,
但是你也可以邀请我们进去 招待我们
but you can also just invite us in for a treat.
赶紧离开 否则走着瞧
Leave now or else.
我们进去给他来个万圣节大惊吓吧
Let's go inside and give him a good Halloween scare.
他去哪儿了?
Where'd he go?
你看见那玩意了吗?
Did you see that?
嗨 女士们
Hi, ladies.
欢迎来到谋杀屋
Welcome to Murder House,
你们随时可以进来参观
where you can check in anytime you like
但你们永远不能离开
but you can never leave.
你们得帮我们逃出这里 求求你们了
You have to help us out of here. Please.
‐求你们 救救我们吧 ‐他们救不了我们
‐Please, help us. ‐They can't help us.
没人能救得了我们
No one can.
我们是在这里被杀死的 所以我们永远逃不出去
We were killed here, so we can never escape.
很抱歉 但她说得对
Sorry, but she's right.
如果你们死在这里 你们将被永远困在这里
If you die here, you're trapped here forever.
也许我们应该试着帮她们一下
Maybe we're supposed to try and help them, though.
这体验可以被叫做"谋杀屋逃离记"
I mean, it is called the "Escape from Murder House Experience."
‐求你们了 ‐求求你们 帮帮我们吧
‐ Please. ‐ Please, help us.
注释：Infantata：出自《美国恐怖故事第一季：谋杀屋》
是塔塔怪婴
It's the Infantata.
这血迹是真的吗?
Is that fake blood?
‐它把我划伤了 他妈的真划伤了 ‐这不对劲!
‐It cut me. It really fucking cut me. ‐This isn't right!
‐请停下! ‐我们不喜欢这样! 太过了!
‐ Please, stop! ‐ We don't like it! It's too much!
我们要停下! 求你们了! 现在就停下!
And we want it to stop! Please! Now!
请停下! 我们不喜欢这样! 太逼真了!
Please, stop! We don't like it! It's too real!
你们不应该伤害我们!
You're not supposed to hurt us!
这不是假的 这是真的!
It's not fake. It's real!
出去!
Get out of here!
快!
Now!
不!
No!
我告诉过你你 无脑贱人 你会死在里面的
I told you, dumb bitch. You're gonna die in here.
你在这里干嘛? 你不是死在街上了吗!
What are you doing here? You died on the street!
我们都是从四面八方聚集到这来的
We've all come here from all over.
‐今天是个特殊的日子 ‐什么日子?
‐It's a special occasion. ‐What occasion?
你死的日子
The day you die.
这是不可能的!
This isn't possible!
你们全都不该出现在这里!
None of you should be here!
求你了 停止这一切!
Please, make this stop!
注释：恐怖小丑：《美国恐怖故事第四季：畸形秀》角色，杀人如麻，手法残忍。
你被恐怖小丑击杀
You were killed by Twisty.
游戏结束
你现在被永远困在谋杀屋了
You are now trapped in the Murder House forever.
这操作器太烂了 一直在出现故障
These controls suck. It keeps glitching.
我本来可以逃出去的 但是正当我试图逃跑的时候
I could have escaped, but it froze up again right when
‐它就卡住了 ‐好吧 听着 这个很容易修复的
‐I tried to run. ‐Okay. I mean, look, that's an easy fix.
但整体上你觉得怎么样
But what do you think in general?
拜托 画面很棒 不是吗?
Come on, the graphics are amazing, aren't they?
是的
Yeah.
但是呢?
But?
别误会
Don't take this the wrong way,
但是 你真的有去看过这部剧吗?
but, like, have you even ever actually watched the show?
是的 我看了这部剧 虽然我没像你
Yes, I've watched the show. I'm not an obsessive fan
这么着迷 但是……我确实看过这部剧
like you, but... I've watched the show.
就算最佛的粉丝都会被气走
Even casual fans of the show are gonna be pissed
因为阿迪在里面是个鬼魂
because Addie is a ghost there
还有其他几季的其他角色
and there are other characters from other seasons
不可能会到谋杀屋来
who have no business being there.
其次 我认为你可能不知道
Second, I think you're missing the reason
为什么粉丝们这么想回到谋杀屋
why fans keep wanting to go back to Murder House.
并非是说他们想把更多的人困在那里
It's not that they want to trap more people there.
而是他们想要感受新人能不能
They want to feel the tension of whether or not
逃出去的紧张感
the new people are gonna be able to escape or not.
把人们困在这座房子里
The thing that always trips people up in the house
并且引诱他们向下深入 最终被困于此的东西
and leads them down that path to getting stuck there
是他们没做好人的本分
is that they don't deal with their human shit.
他们要么太自私 要么太贪婪
They're too selfish or greedy
要么刻薄 占有欲过强 或者抑郁了
or mean or possessive or depressed,
所以他们被迫待在
so they're forced to stay like that,
或是说被永远困在这座房子里
frozen in the house forever.
行吧 我明白你的意思了
Okay, I hear you.
但这效果挺恐怖的
But it's scary.
是吧?这还不够吗
Right? Isn't it enough
如果 如果把它们放置于同一背景 不还是很可怕吗?
if‐if it's in the same basic setting but it's scary?
我不知道
I don't know.
注释：Jaws 2（《大白鲨2》）：是对经典原作的苍白模仿，对观众而言毫无悬念。
可能这就是人们为什么想拍《大白鲨2》吧
That's exactly what the people who made Jaws 2 thought.
好吧 呃…
Okay. Um...
我竭尽全力了
I put everything into this.
我辞职 就为了专心研发它 我把房子抵押出去了
I quit my job to develop it. I mortgaged the house
就为了能雇到程序员
so that I could hire the programmers
他们在我们的车库里昼夜不停地工作
who have been working in our garage day and night.
我需要用它来黏合我们的关系 黏合我们整个家庭
I need this to work out for us. For our family.
‐这一切又不是我强迫你做的 ‐我做这一切
‐I didn't ask you to do any of this. ‐I did this
是为了你 因为我觉得…
for you because I thought...
我觉得我们能通过你最爱的剧来重归于好
I thought we could bond over your favorite show.
你陪我看看就行了啊
You could've just watched it with me.
我爱你 妈妈 但是你并不是真的懂得这部剧的精髓
I love you, Mom, but you don't really get the vibe of the show.
一点……也不懂
Like... at all.
你是再说 我一点也不懂你
You're saying I don't get you at all.
我在努力了
I'm trying.
等等 亲爱的 你要去哪儿?
Wait, honey. Where are you going?
我点了汉堡外卖
I got HiHo burgers from Postmates.
你要去哪儿?
Where you going?
我今晚要住在爸爸家
I'm gonna stay at Dad's tonight.
事实上 我想我要在那里待上几周吧
Actually, I think I'm gonna stay there for a couple of weeks.
最近这里的事情
Things have gotten
变得很奇怪
so weird around here lately.
罗里
Rory.
园艺剪刀
Garden shears.
无处可逃
There's no escape.
通常我会等到参观结束时
Usually I wait until the end of the tour
再说坏消息 但是…
to give the bad news, but...
都家喻户晓了 何必呢?
why bother delaying the inevitable?
一年多前 他们在这座房子里发现了九具尸体
They found nine bodies in the house a year or so ago.
我知道
I know.
我还知道有具尸体是鲁比·麦克丹尼尔
And I know about the body of that girl Ruby McDaniel
他们一个月前在后院里发现的
they found in the backyard a month later.
噢 上帝
Oh, God.
你该不会是那些热衷于谋杀案的粉丝
You're not one of those murder nerds
只是想到房子里来几张自拍
who's just here to take Instagram selfies
发到Instagram上吧? 因为我知道
inside the house? Because I know.
我知道这是全美在售的最烂的房子
I know this is the shittiest listing in America, and I know
还有 我被这栋烂房子缠上
that it says a lot about what the other agents at my office
很能说明我办公室里的其他职员 对我的看法
think about me that I'm the one who's stuck with it,
但是抱歉 对待工作我是认真的
but I'm sorry. I take my job seriously.
对我来说 任何一座在售的房子
To me, every listing
就是 是一个在寻找新家庭的孤儿
is‐is a little orphan child looking for a new family
希望能被收养 确实 这个孩子还自带行李
to adopt it. And, yes, this one has some baggage
还有一些真正的传闻
and some real issues,
但它也同样值得被爱
but it is no less deserving of love.
‐多少钱?‐你认真的?
‐How much? ‐Seriously?
我是在投资
It's an investment.
好吧 呃 你很幸运
Okay. Uh, well, you're in luck.
银行基本上是打算单以地价售卖这座房子
The bank is basically willing to sell it for land value.
那是多少钱?
How much is that?
60万美元
$600,000.
但是 对他们来说很不幸的是
But, unfortunately for them,
没有人愿意买
no one's been willing to pay that,
‐所以他们愿意接受任何出价 10万美元
‐so they are open to any offers. ‐$100,000.
我得打个电话
I need to make a call,
但我想你刚刚已经成功把房子买下了
but I think you just bought yourself a house.
当然 恕不退还
As is, of course.
这玩意儿比废料排放场
This thing is harder to move
还难搬
than a toxic waste dump.
珍妮? 嗨 嗨 是啊 我想我找到人
Jenny? Hi. Hi. Yeah, I think I found someone
收养我们的小怪崽房子了
to adopt our little devil baby house.
没有意外
No contingencies.
你现在是我的了
You're mine.
我会让你向我袒露一切秘密的
I am going to make you reveal all your secrets to me.
罗里 亲爱的 你看起来真可爱
Rory. Honey, you look so cute.
‐瞧瞧你 ‐妈
‐ Look at you. ‐ Mom.
‐你来干嘛? ‐噢 呃 我就给你多送点衣服
‐What are you doing here? ‐Oh, um, I just brought you some extra clothes.
我会出趟远门 要一周左右
I am gonna be going away for about a week or so.
去哪里?
Where?
我要去参加万圣节恐怖大会
I'm going to a Halloween horror convention.
《美国恐怖故事》的编剧们会发表谈话
The writers of American Horror Story are doing a talk.
我要向他们问问关于谋杀屋里的一切
I'm gonna ask them to tell me all about Murder House.
这就是 最重要的环节
What it means, what the most important aspects are.
嘿 我在听取你的意见
Hey, I'm taking your advice.
我在努力尝试理解精髓
I'm trying to figure out the vibe.
亲耳去听 听方为实
Right from the horse's mouth.
‐史蒂文 ‐米歇尔
‐Steven. ‐Michelle.
抱歉 我只是无意中听到
I'm sorry, I just overheard
‐你刚和罗里说的 ‐是啊 我也很抱歉
‐what you were telling Rory. ‐Yeah, I'm sorry, too,
因为这不关你的事
'cause it's none of your business.
当你破产
Well, when you go broke
我得一人供养罗里的时候
and I have to pay for everything for Rory,
就与我有关了
it will be my business.
罗里 能让我和你爸爸单独谈谈吗?
Rory, can you give your dad and I a moment?
不 他应该听听 米歇尔
No. He should hear this. Michelle,
你太不切实际了
you're in over your head.
你又陷入某种狂热之中了
You're on one of your obsessive kicks again.
你搞出幺蛾子 还蒙上双眼
You pull this shit, and you get blinders on,
然后走啊 走啊 走啊
and you go, and you go, and you go
‐一直走到悬崖边也不肯停下 ‐你知道的
‐until you drive yourself straight off a cliff. ‐You know,
对于你还是总想指责我的梦想
I'm sorry that you've always felt the need
我感到很抱歉 但我们不再是夫妻了
to dump on my dreams, but we're not married anymore,
所以我能不用考虑你的想法就去做
so I can do without your opinion.
非常感谢你 史蒂文
Thank you so much, Steven.
如果你能不要再怀恨在心 仿佛那是血海深仇
If you could just look past that giant chip on your shoulder,
你就会明白我只是想帮你
it would be so clear to you that I'm just trying to help you.
我曾经娶了你 我爱你
I was married to you, and I love you
尽管发生了这一切
in spite of everything that happened,
我看清了你
and I see you.
如果说你有一个致命的缺点
And if you've got one fatal flaw,
那就是你过于确信
it's that you're so convinced
有什么东西等待你去证明
that you've got something to prove
就算你身死陨首 也非要去证明一番
that you will kill yourself to prove it.
如果我是个男人 那就叫雄心壮志
And if I were a man, that would be called drive.
甚至是令人钦佩的雄心壮志
Admirable ambition, even.
得了吧 米歇尔
Come on, Michelle.
亲爱的 你能把这个给你爸吗?
Can you give that to your father, sweetie?
给我们一点时间?
Give us a moment?
这次旅行会解决我们所有的烦恼
This trip is gonna be the answer to all our worries.
妈妈 爸爸是对的
Dad's right, Mom.
你不需要向我证明什么
You don't have to prove anything to me.
我觉得你棒极了
I think you're awesome.
谢谢你 我的好孩子
Thank you, my sweet boy.
‐我爱你 ‐我也爱你
‐I love you. ‐Love you, too.
好吧
Okay.
你玩得开心
You have fun.
你会死在里面的
You're gonna die in there.
那么 你们的计划是?
So, what's your guys's plan?
我要去夜店
I'm going to the club.
想要一个没死的老二
Desperate for some dick
想了十几年了
that hasn't been dead for a decade.
我也是
Same.
我要去看我的兄弟
I'm going to see my brother.
我要去看看大海
I'm just gonna go look at the ocean.
我想我已经开始对死亡感到沮丧了
Think I'm starting to get depressed about being dead.
如果我是你 我就不会进去
I wouldn't go in there if I were you.
那里面已经挤得要死了
It's already crowded as fuck.
‐我能帮你点什么? ‐嗨
‐ Can I help you? ‐ Hi.
你们是为了万圣节才打扮的吗?
Do you guys just dress up in time for Halloween?
你是狂热粉丝吗?
Are you superfans?
‐什么的狂热粉丝? ‐得了吧 宝贝!
‐ Superfans of what? ‐ Come on, babe!
时间不等人
Time's a‐wasting.
先进来待一会儿
Come in for a little bit first.
噢 呃…你好?
Oh, um... Hello?
等等
Wait.
有人吗?
Hello?
有人在吗?
Anyone?
有人吗?我是米歇尔
Hello? I'm Michelle.
新房主
The new owner.
有人吗?
Hello?
出来 出来吧 无论你们在哪里
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
有人吗?有人吗?我想如果你们在这
Hello? Hello? I assume if you're here
你们就是狂热粉
that you're superfans.
我知道你们能听到我
I know you can hear me.
很乐意和你们聊聊节目的事
Love to chat with you about the show.
有人吗?
Hello?
我正在制作一款基于谋杀屋的游戏
I'm making a game based on the Murder House.
我知道你们在这
I know you're here.
我只是想试图理解精髓 拜托?
I'm just trying to understand the vibe. Please?
不管那意味着什么
Whatever that means.
有人吗?
Hello?
有人在吗?
Anyone?
有人吗?
Hello?
如果你能逃出这座房子
If you could escape this house‐‐
不是逃到外面的世界 而是一个…
not out in the world but, like, in a...
能让你的灵魂安息的地方
put your soul to rest kind of way‐‐
你会这么做吗?
would you do it?
也许在我遇见你之前的几年前我会这么想
Maybe a few years ago before I met you.
只要这里永远有你在 我就不介意永远地继续待下去
I don't mind going on forever as long as forever includes you.
‐你想要让我解脱吗? ‐不
‐Would you want that? ‐No.
即使这意味着你父亲们也能自由和解脱?
Not even if it meant freedom and relief for your dads?
让我的爸爸们见鬼去吧
Fuck my dads.
让这里所有的鬼魂见鬼去吧
Fuck every ghost in here.
让所有不是你和我的家伙
Fuck anyone and everyone
都见鬼去吧
who isn't you or me.
天啊 外面活人的世界是如此的艰难
God, life is rough out in the world of living.
我不需要钱 但为了不光靠
I don't need money, but I took a shit job at Erewhon
看家庭赛乐赛这个节目来打发日子
just to have something to do with my days
我在Erewohn找了份差劲的工作
besides watch Family Feud.
我的生活基本上就是在
My life is basically just waiting
等待每年的万圣节的过程中度过的
for Halloween to roll around every year.
如果不是盼望着你
If I didn't have you to look forward to,
我压根都不想活着
I wouldn't want to be alive at all.
我不会让任何事耽误我们在一起的时间
I won't let anything get in the way of our time together.
即使你会保持年轻性感 而我会
Even though you're gonna stay young and hot and I'm gonna get
‐变老和长满皱纹?‐噢 阴毛都变灰白
‐old and wrinkly? ‐Oh, bring on the gray pubes.
我爱你 我爱你
‐I love you. ‐I love you.
让我们去制造些麻烦吧
Let's go cause some trouble.
有人吗?
Hello?
对不起
Sorry.
我通常只有自慰后才会这样哭
I usually only cry like this after I masturbate.
什么?
Pardon?
没什么
Nothing.
你不是前几天我看到的和房地产经纪人
Aren't you that lady I saw talking to the Realtor
交谈的那位女士吗?
the other day?
你不会真的买下了这个地方吧?
You didn't actually buy this place, did you?
不 呃…
No. Um...
我只是得找个办法进来
I just needed to find a way to get in.
交易永远不会结束
Deal's never gonna close.
呃 其实我没有钱
Um, I don't actually have the money.
我在制作一款电子游戏
I'm making a video game,
但我陷入了创作困境
and I am creatively stuck, and this is
而这是我最后一次尝试获得某种灵感
my last effort at getting some sort of inspiration.
我真的不知道还他妈能做些什么了
I actually don't know what else to fucking do.
它暴力吗?
Is it violent?
因为我一直劝告家长们
Because I've always counseled parents
暴力电子游戏会对孩子们造成危害
that violent video games are terrible for children.
等等
Wait a minute.
你是 呃……?
Aren't you, um...?
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
偿还我的罪孽
Paying for my sins.
就像这鬼地方的其他人一样
Just like everyone else in this godforsaken place.
你知道什么是永恒幸福
You know what's a bad combination
的坏组合吗?
for eternal happiness?
你的妻子 你永远十几岁的女儿
Your wife, your forever teenaged daughter,
她的男朋友 一个新生儿
her boyfriend, a newborn
还有你以前的情妇
and your former mistress all trapped
都被困在同一所房子里
in the same house together.
好吧 这肯定是个玩笑 对吧?
Okay, this has got to be some kind of joke, right?
我是说 你在这做什么的?
I mean, what do you do? Do you just
你是不是在万圣节晚上
come in here and fuck with people
来这跟偷溜进来的人上床?是吗?
on Halloween night who sneak in? Right?
这是什么都不可能是个笑话
It's the farthest thing from a joke.
我身处地狱
I'm in hell.
别像这里的另一个治疗师一样
And don't start telling me it's all my fault
跟我说这都是我的错
like that other therapist in here.
我不想背着我妻子乱搞
I didn't want to cheat on my wife.
我在这所房子里
I resisted for years
忍了好几年了
in this house.
注释：Hayden（海登）：《美国恐怖故事第一季：谋杀屋》人物。
但海登真的很固执
But Hayden is really persistent,
注释：Vivien（薇薇安）：《美国恐怖故事第一季：谋杀屋》人物，这位男士的妻子。
薇薇安有时也会如此挑剔
and Vivien can be so judgy and sullen
‐阴沉 ‐所以 你因为出轨
‐sometimes. ‐So, you're blaming the women in your life
在责怪你生活中的女人们?好吧
for you being a cheater? Okay.
如果你不为自己的行为负责
Um, you can never actually find forgiveness
你永远也得不到宽恕
if you don't take responsibility for your own actions.
我只是再说生活是复杂的
I'm just saying life is complicated.
很显然 死亡也是
And so is death, apparently.
问题是
The problem was
我一直以为我可以拥有一切
I always thought I could have it all.
妻子和情妇
A wife and a mistress.
家庭和我房子外的生活
A family and a life outside my house.
所以我死在这儿
So I ended up here
一无所有
with nothing.
从你脸上的表情判断
Judging by that look on your face,
我的专业意见是你被出轨了
my professional opinion is that you were cheated on.
‐你看起来很激动 ‐不 呃…
‐You look triggered. ‐No. Uh...
事实上 史蒂文对我是忠诚的
Actually, uh, Steven was faithful.
我评判你只是因为 我不知道 因为我能
I'm judging you just because, I don't know, I can.
我才是我婚姻中的那个麻烦
The trouble in my marriage was me,
老实说
if I want to be honest.
好吧?我总是欲求不满
Okay? I like to want things,
然后我就会痴迷于得到它们
and then I get obsessed about getting them.
这在求爱过程中很有吸引力
It's compelling in a courtship.
每个人都想要被需要的感觉
Everybody wants to feel like they're wanted.
‐嗯 ‐一旦我真的得到了 我就不会那么棒了
‐Hmm. ‐I'm just not so great once I actually get it
因为 呃 随着时间的推移 我…
'cause, um, over time, I...
我感到无聊
I get bored.
然后我就会变得很伤人
And then I can be quite hurtful.
你喜欢饥渴而不是满足的感觉
You like being hungry more than being fed.
没错
Yes.
没错 没错 没错
Yes, yes, yes.
好吧 那么……
Okay, so, here's...
我现在真正渴望的是理解
What I'm really hungering for now is an understanding.
告诉我…告诉我这地方是什么样子 我是说
Tell me... Tell me what this place is like. I mean,
我想知道在这里的真实感觉
I want to know what it truly feels like to be here
感受渴望 恐惧
and to feel the‐the longing and the‐the fear,
‐还有乐趣 ‐乐趣?
‐the fun. ‐Fun?
当你听的唱片一次又一次的重播时
Is it fun when the record
会有趣吗?
you're listening to skips over and over?
几十年来都坐在旋转木马上 会有趣吗?
Is it fun being on a merry‐go‐round for decades?
不
No.
呃 我…我在设计一款电子游戏
Uh, I'm... I'm designing a video game.
要想成功 它必须要有趣
And for it to work, it's got to be fun.
它得有意义
It's got to have purpose.
你知道 必须得有意义
You know, there's got to be a point so that the player's
‐这样玩家才会想继续玩 ‐这里漫无目的
‐gonna want to continue playing. ‐There is no purpose here.
这里毫无意义
There is no point in here.
这里只有无法逃离的无尽枯燥
It's just endless dull with no escape.
我们不在地狱里 这只是
We're not in hell. It's an old house
洛杉矶某个街区的一座老房子
in a neighborhood in L. A.
你知道 它周围都是很普通的房子
You know, it's surrounded by perfectly normal houses.
这一定是有意义的 对吧?
There's got to be a point, right?
我是说 也许甚至有办法逃走
I mean, maybe there's even a way to escape.
只是还没人知道该怎么做
It's just nobody's figured out how yet.
你知道 我儿子说 被困在这里的人之所以无法逃脱
You know, my son says that, uh, the people who are trapped here
可能是因为他们活着的时候从来没能解决自己的问题
are probably stuck because they never resolved their issues
所以他们受到的伤害变成了他们的命运
when they were alive, so their damage becomes their destiny.
也许关键在于你们必须学习和成长
Maybe the point is that you have to learn and grow,
这样你们才能解脱
and only then can you escape.
所以你觉得如果我对每一个鬼魂
So you think if I have intense therapy sessions
都进行大强度的心理治疗
with each of the ghosts,
注释：普通人 潮浪王子 都是讲主角通过找心理医生进行心理治疗并走出困境的电影
他们就会产生一些像电影普通人
they'll have some kind of Ordinary People,
和潮浪王子那样的重大进展
Prince of Tides breakthrough
并找到精神上的平静?
and find spiritual peace?
抱歉
Sorry.
那不可能发生 我被困在这里后
Not gonna happen. I tried that with Tate
我和塔特试过了
after I got stuck here,
他还是和以前一样疯狂
and he's just as bananas as he's always been.
好吧 呃…
Okay. Um...
呃…
Well...
呃 我能和
Um, can I speak to somebody
不那么迷失和绝望的人谈谈吗?
who's maybe not so lost and hopeless?
那你可来错地儿了
Then you've come to the wrong house.
好吧
Okay.
呃…
Um...
我们能帮你点什么?
Can we help you?
呃 是的
Um, yes.
我试图理解这个地方的精髓
I'm trying to understand the vibe of this place,
但我真正了解的是 与之相关的每个人
but all I'm really getting is that everybody
都太疯狂了
associated with it is just... really crazy.
注释：True Blood《真爱如血》是一部共有7季80集的美国电视剧。
我只是要做一款关于《真爱如血》的电子游戏或者…
I'm just gonna make a video game about True Blood or...
‐一些正常的东西 ‐你想真正理解这里吗?
‐something normal. ‐You want to get the vibe?
以下是关于这个地方你需要了解的
Here's what you need to understand about this place.
是的 是有一些鬼魂想出去
Yes, there are a few spirits who want out,
但这里还有其他鬼魂对成长不感兴趣
but there are others here who have no interest in growth,
我们接受自己有多完蛋
who embrace how fucked‐up we all are.
现在 比起被困在自己的痛苦中
Now, the only thing that we love more
我们唯一更爱的事情
than being stuck in our own misery
就算和那些更悲惨的笨蛋
is being stuck here
一起被困在这里
with the suckers who are even more miserable.
重复就是意义
The repetition is the point.
充斥着痛苦的无尽虚无
The endless nothing filled with pain
就是目的
is the purpose.
我们唯一需要的东西
The only thing that we need
就是用更多的灵魂来滋养痛苦
is more souls to feed the suffering.
该死
Shit.
‐多少? ‐作为你的治疗师
‐What? ‐As your therapist,
我的专业意见是
my professional opinion is
‐你应该拼命地逃 ‐什么?
‐that you should run like hell. ‐What?
呃…
Uh...
你根本不了解这个地方
You really don't understand this place at all.
现在就离开 否则你将被迫永远理解这个地方
Leave now or you're gonna be forced to understand forever.
轮到你了
It's your turn.
又死了
Dead again.
说“不给糖就捣蛋”
Say "trick or treat."
嗨 宝贝
Hi, baby.
哦
Oh.
不
No.
拜托别这样 我们只有一晚能在一起
Please don't do that. We have one night together.
他们花了一个星期才找到你的尸体
It took a week for them to find your body.
我们甚至都不知道你失踪了三天
We didn't even know you were missing for three days
因为你撒谎
because you lied
还说你要去参加恐怖大会
and said you were going to a horror convention.
‐我很抱歉 我不想让你担心 ‐扯淡
‐I'm sorry. I didn't want you to worry. ‐Bullshit.
你不想让我试图阻止你
You didn't want me to try and stop you.
直到我们开始接到电话
It wasn't until we started getting calls
我们发现你想买房子
that we found out you tried to buy a house.
我一听到这个消息 就知道你在哪里
As soon as I heard that, I knew where you were.
我再也见不到你了
That I was never gonna see you again.
你那愚蠢的痴迷
That your stupid fucking obsession
‐把你给害死了 ‐听我说 嘿
‐got you killed. ‐Listen to me. Hey.
我只是想为我们做点特别的事
I just wanted to build something special for us.
我只是想让你感到骄傲
I just wanted to make you proud.
通过制作电子游戏?
By making a video game?
你知道你该怎么做才能打动我吗?
You know what you could have done to impress me?
如果你去看一个他妈的心理医生
If you had went to a fucking shrink
处理好你的破事儿
and dealt with your shit.
如果你向我展示 人是可以改变的
If you had shown me that people can change.
如果你在意识到自己做不到的时候 就停止制作这个该死的游戏
I would've been more proud if you quit making the fucking game
而不是让你自己他妈的被杀
once you realized that you couldn't do it,
若不是你被你的痴迷所困住
rather than getting yourself fucking killed
我本会更自豪的
because you‐you get so trapped by your obsessions.
嘿 现在说太晚了
Hey. It's too late for that.
已经太晚了 听着 我…
It's too late for that. Look, I'm...
我已经被困住了 好吗
I'm stuck as I am, okay? I'm stuck
我被困在那儿了
in that place.
没有办法能逃出谋杀屋
There's no escaping the Murder House.
我认为有办法
I think there is.
‐怎么做? ‐火
‐How? ‐Fire.
火能净化一切 你需要烧掉它
Fire purifies everything. You need to burn,
把那破房子烧的片甲不留
burn that motherfucker to the ground.
我非常乐意做这项工作
And I'm more than happy to do the job.
听我的 如果你那么做了
Listen to me. If you do that,
如果它成功的话
if it works,
我就会离开
I'm gone.
我…
I...
我再也不能见到你了 好吧?
I don't see you ever again. Okay?
你很久以前就离开我了
You were gone from me a long time ago.
再说 是时候
Besides, it's time
结束那座房子所造成的一切痛苦了
for all of the misery of that house to end.
我再也不想看到或听到
I never want to see or hear
‐任何一件关于谋杀屋的事了 ‐好吧
‐one more thing about Murder House again. ‐Okay.
但是 你看 那里也有好人
But, look, there's good people in there.
他们正努力过着充实的生活
They're trying to live their productive lives,
不管那意味着什么
whatever that means.
就答应我
Just promise me
你不会对那房子做任何事 好吗?
you're not gonna do anything to that house, okay?
答应我
Promise me.
好吧
Fine.
‐嘿 嘿 ‐什么?
‐Hey. Hey. ‐What?
你为什么不打扮一下?
Why aren't you dressed up?
我再也不喜欢万圣节了
I don't like Halloween anymore.
你们进来吗?
You guys coming inside?
‐我们喜欢按照自己的方式道别 ‐嘿
‐We like to do it our own way. ‐Hey.
抱歉把你困在里面
Sorry about trapping you in there.
虽然你拿着刀 但我其实是自作自受
You held the knife, but I did it to myself, really.
离日出还有十秒
Ten seconds to sunrise.
‐这他妈的是什么? ‐噢 不
‐The fuck is this? ‐Oh, no.
‐你认识他? ‐他是我儿子
‐ You know him? ‐ He's my son.
他想把房子烧了
He's trying to burn the house down.
认为这会让所有的灵魂自由
Thinks it's gonna free all the spirits.
会吗?
Will it?
天啊 我希望如此
God, I hope so.
那我们这些不想自由的人呢?
Well, what about those of us who don't want to be free?
我今天不需要这烂事儿
I do not need this shit today.
罗里
Rory.
我觉得你和你儿子真的应该考虑
I think you and your son should really consider
一些家庭心理治疗 现在 我知道你们已经见过本·哈蒙了
some family therapy. Now, I know that you've already met
但我可以向你保证
with Ben Harmon, but I can assure you
‐和我一起你会看到更好的成果 ‐走开
‐you'll see much better results with me. ‐Move.
坦白说 他没那么厉害
Quite frankly, he's just not that good.
我随时都有空
I'm available anytime.
我要将他开膛破肚 让他慢慢失血
I'm gonna gut him but make sure he bleeds out slowly enough
趁他死之前 把他扔出去
to throw him off the property. The last thing we need is
‐我们最不希望的就是这儿再多一个麻烦精 ‐不!
‐ another troublemaker in here. ‐ No!
对不起了 鲁比
Sorry, Ruby.
虽然你和斯嘉丽彼此相爱
What you and Scarlett had was so lovely,
但我们现在该走了
but it's time for us to go now.
我们再也受不了了
We can't take it anymore.
‐我只想要这一切结束 ‐你们这些愚蠢的婊子
‐ I just need it to be over. ‐ You stupid bitches.
你不明白这意味着什么吗?
Don't you understand what that means?
我们会化作虚无!
It means we become nothing!
虚无也比永生更好
Nothing is better than this for all eternity.
好样的!
Attaboy.
燃吧 宝贝 燃吧
Burn, baby, burn.
哈蒙医生
Dr. Harmon.
唱片不断卡带
And the record kept skipping
一遍 一遍……
over and over...
．．.又一遍
...and over.
我很抱歉 才怪
Sorry. Not sorry.
我能来份早餐墨西哥卷饼 一杯新鲜橙汁
Yeah, can I get a breakfast burrito, a fresh orange juice,
哦 还有个苹果派吗?
oh, and an apple pie?
你确定这是你想要的?
Are you sure this is what you want?
是的
Yes.
我想你已经找到结束游戏的方法了
Guess you figured out a way to end the video game.
它将会是畅销游戏
It'll be a best seller.
我敢肯定
I'm sure of it.
再见 妈妈
Goodbye, Mom.
再见 我的好孩子
Bye, my sweet boy.
妈妈!
Mom!
不!快动手!点燃它!
No! Do it! Light it up!
做吧 宝贝 动手吧!
Do it, baby, do it!
不!不!不!
No! No! No!
‐不!‐不!
‐No! ‐No!
求你了
Please.
‐不! ‐快动手
‐ No! ‐ Do it.
动手啊!
Do it!
鲁比!
Ruby!
斯嘉丽
Scarlett.
跟我一起死吧!
Die with me!
鬼魂不是问题所在
Well, the ghosts weren't the problem.
都怪那些该死的电视剧粉丝
It was the damn TV show fans
整天源源不断地来这里自拍
that kept coming here at all hours to take selfies.
嘿 混蛋们
Hey, assholes,
它只是间房子
it's just a house.
大火已被扑灭
The fire is out
还剩下一些余烬
except for some smoldering remnants.
就像这样
And just like that,
洛杉矶 或许甚至是全世界 最臭名昭著的房子之一
one of the most notorious houses in all of Los Angeles‐‐
终于彻底消失了
maybe the world‐‐ is finally gone for good.
‐你一定是斯嘉丽 是的 嗨
‐You must be Scarlett. ‐Yes. Hi.
我带你看看这套房子吧
Let me show you the unit.
如你所见 开发商们
As you can see, the developers
不惜工本打造了这座房子
spared no expense.
这套房子里所有的东西都是最高端的
Everything in this unit is state‐of‐the‐art,
这些更是绝妙无比
and these are divine.
‐建筑师们花了……提姆
‐The architect went... ‐Tim.
我们之间能坦诚相待吗?
Can we have an honest relationship?
好的 没问题
Yeah, okay.
你有告诉过
Do you tell people
来看新房子的人
who are looking at these new condo units
这地方是圣地吗?
that these grounds are hallowed?
圣地?
Hallowed?
好吧 好几十人死在了这里
Well, dozens of people died here.
都是些重要的人
People who mattered.
直到那场大火
Until the fire.
你有告诉过那些潜在的买主
Do you tell potential buyers
这幢公寓大楼
that this building of condominiums
曾经是谋杀屋吗?
used to be the Murder House?
事实上 没有
Actually, no.
不 我没有
No, I don't.
‐为什么不呢? ‐好吧 说实话
‐Why not? ‐Well, to be honest‐‐
既然你让我坦诚相待
since that's what we're aiming for‐‐
一开始
at first,
我很犹豫
I was torn.
我已经卖了五套房了 而且我没跟住户说过
I sold the first five units, and I said nothing
这个地方曾经是谋杀屋
about that place that used to be here.
但住户们已经在这个公寓里呆了半年多了
But people have been living in this new building now
我有向他们确认过
for over six months, and I check in on my customers.
没有人受到伤害
No one has been harmed.
没有人看到幽灵
There have been no apparition sightings.
我相信
I believe
那场大火净化了那间屋子里的
that the fire purified whatever occult forces
神秘力量
were contained within those walls.
我也认为那些灵魂
And I also believe that those spirits
随便你怎么称呼他们
or whatever you want to call them
都已经自由了
are finally free.
这是最后一间了 是吗?
And this is the last unit, correct?
没错
Yeah.
我买了
I'll take it.
现金全款
All cash.
你要支付一百万美金
You'll pay $1 million
全用现金吗?
all cash?
就你这个年纪大的小姑娘?
A young woman your age?
我很抱歉 我能问问你是怎么弄到那么多钱的吗?
I'm sorry, may I ask how you got that kind of money?
我利用毕生所长
I utilized my greatest life skill
成为了一名雇佣杀手
and became a hired assassin.
我现在半退休了
I'm semiretired now.
谁知道呢 没准我哪天又开始重操旧业了?
Maybe I'll go back to it one day. Who knows?
杀坏人既赚钱
But it was lucrative
又有趣
and fun killing bad people.
别那么惊讶地看着我 提姆 我告诉过你
Don't look so shocked, Tim. I told you
我想坦诚相待
I wanted an honest relationship.
好吧 斯嘉丽
Okay, Scarlett.
我会起草合同的 这栋房子是你了
I'll draw up the papers. This unit is officially yours.
♪ 我们为何不去散个步呢? ♪
♪ Why don't we take a walk? ♪
♪ 所有人知道 我们只需有人指点迷津 ♪
♪ Everybody knows a hand to hold is all we need ♪
♪ 安静 别说话 ♪
♪ Quiet, let's not even talk ♪
♪ 我对你所说的每个词 ♪
♪ Every word I say to you ♪
♪ 你只要重复就行 ♪
♪ You only just repeat ♪
♪ 当你看向镜子时 ♪
♪ And when you're looking in the mirror ♪
♪ 恶魔可能比看起来更近 ♪
♪ Demons may be closer than they may appear ♪
♪ 你可以哭着 坐着 盯着 ♪
♪ You can either cry and sit and stare ♪
♪ 或者试着逃离 ♪
♪ Or try to run away ♪
♪ 我会试着逃离 ♪
♪ I'm trying to run away ♪
♪ 我凝视着鬼魂 ♪
♪ I'm staring at a ghost ♪
♪ 当你看向镜子的时候 ♪
♪ And when you're looking in the mirror ♪
♪ 恶魔可能比看起来更近 ♪
♪ Demons may be closer than they may appear ♪
♪ 你可以哭着 坐着 盯着 ♪
♪ You can either cry and sit and stare ♪
♪ 或者试着逃离 ♪
♪ Or try to run away ♪
♪ 我会试着逃离 ♪
♪ I'm trying to run away ♪
♪ 我凝视着鬼魂 ♪
♪ I'm staring at a ghost. ♪
鲁比 ?
Ruby?
我在这里
I'm here.
我终于准备好和你在一起了
I'm finally ready to be with you.
永远在一起
Forever.
但为时已晚 我觉悟太迟
But I'm too late.
你已经永远离去了
You're gone forever.
其他人在哪里?
Where are the others?
我爸爸呢?
My dads?
他们走了
They're gone.
他们选择继续前行
They chose to move on.
我看见他们走了
I saw them go.
他们看上去很开心 至少大多数人是那样
They seemed happy. Most of them did, at least.
你为什么还在这里?
Why are you still here?
我是唯一一个想留下的人
I was the only one who wanted to stay.
为你 斯嘉丽
For you, Scarlett.
我知道你会回到我身边
I knew you'd come back to me.
真爱不死
True love never dies.
胜利 你逃离了谋杀屋
Success. You escaped Murder House.
哦!
Oh!
所以? 你觉得呢?
So? What do you think?
2.0版本 有你想要的那种精髓吗?
Version 2.0. I mean, does it get the vibe?
绝对有 比上一版好多了
Totally. It's so much better.
但我觉得你得让
But I think you need to have a level
那个小孩从至尊女巫那
where the kid gets, like, a magic potion
拿到魔药
from the Supremes
并帮助她烧毁那间屋子那一关 上升个层次
to help burn the house down or‐or something.
我觉得那样会很好 可以加大游戏的难度
I'd like to see that. I think it'd make the game harder.
我 我 已经没钱了 所以…
I mean, I‐I couldn't afford it, so...
如果我们卖掉这个游戏 也许今后可以给游戏做个更新
If we sell it, though, we can maybe do it as an update
‐之类的 ‐好吧 你至少把手柄的故障修好了
‐or something. ‐Well, at least you fixed the glitches in the controls.
‐哦 我有吗? ‐是我修好了故障吗?
‐ Oh, did I? ‐ Did I fix the glitches?
是的 肯定是你修好的
Yes, I insisted on it.
你真的喜欢吗?
You really like it?
这超酷的
It's super cool.
我真的为你感到骄傲
And I'm really proud of you.
谢谢你 宝贝
Thank you, baby.
‐还想再玩一遍吗?‐不了
‐Want to play again? ‐No.
我想我已经在谋杀屋里待得够久了
I think I've spent enough time in the Murder House.
你想去搞点东西吃吗?
Do you want to go get something to eat?
‐好啊 我饿死了 ‐走吧
‐Yeah, I'm starving. ‐Let's go.
但你觉得
But where do you think
所有被困在谋杀屋的灵魂
all of the spirits who got trapped
都去哪里了呢?
in the Murder House went?
那些想留下来的 留下来了
The ones who wanted to stay stayed,
而那些想走的 已经走了
and the ones who wanted to move on,
他们可能去了天堂或地狱
they maybe went to heaven or hell.
你觉得他们有可能逃到这个世界吗?
Well, do you think any of them escaped into the world?
‐希望不会 ‐嗯
‐Hope not. ‐Hmm.
字幕由WGBH媒体访问组制作
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH